当涉及到纳粹及其军事技术时
When it came down to the Nazis and
their military technology
你无法否认他们是个上一个层次
You can't deny that they were next level
他们制造出蓝鲸大小的迫击炮，
发射出与犀牛一样大的炮弹
They made mortars the size of blue
whales that shot shells as big as rhinos
造了一门又大又强大的火炮
Built an artillery cannon so big and powerful
纳粹自己拆毁了它，因为他们担心
苏联会夺取并利用它对付他们
That the Nazis broke it down themselves,
as they were afraid the Soviets would
capture and use it against them
他们甚至还参与了拆除的原型
And they even worked on a prototype defray
一种能摧毁飞机引擎和飞行员的射线武器
A ray weapon that could kill the
engine of an airplane and its pilot
只需一个简单的点击
With one simple click
纳粹当时正引领着大规模且不合神
的新型战争手段
The Nazis were spearheading massive
and ungodly new means of warfare
在那些大规模毁灭性工厂中
And among those many plants of mass destruction
幸运的是，这部电影从未问世
Was one that, luckily, never saw
the light of day
至少，这个戴软呢帽的家伙不会
At least, not by this fedora-wearing fella
认识那个时代的英雄，或者说主要
反派，吴飞
Meet the hero of its time, or the
main villain, Wu Fei
历史，事实，第四部分。是
Historically, facts, part four. It's